Sometimes students make the best teachers.
Liberal Arts is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Josh Radnor.
Newly single, 35, and uninspired by his job, Jesse Fisher
worries that his best days are behind him.
But no matter how much he buries his head in a
book, life keeps pulling Jesse back.
When his favorite college professor invites him to campus to speak
at his retirement dinner, Jesse jumps at the chance.
Jesse Fisher, played by Josh Radnor.
Zibby, played by Elizabeth Olsen.
Professor Peter Hoberg, played by Richard Jenkins.
Dean, played by John Magaro.
Nat, played by Zac Efron.
Professor Judith Fairfield, played by Allison Janney.
Liberal Arts is a 2012 American comedy-drama film,
written and directed by Josh Radnor.
It tells the story of 35-year-old Jesse (Radnor) who has a romantic
relationship with Zibby (Elizabeth Olsen), a 19-year-old college student.
The film premiered at the 2012 Sundance Film Festival in January 2012.
The film explores themes of age difference,
literature, classical music, college, letter.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.